export const quiz = {
    totalQuestions: 10,
    questions: [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "52 - 32 =?",
        "answers": ["10", "40", "20", "30"],
        "correctAnswer": "20"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "40 - 17 =?",
        "answers": ["25", "13", "23", "33"],
        "correctAnswer": "23"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "13 - 8 =?",
        "answers": ["7", "5", "2", "3"],
        "correctAnswer": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "8 - 5 =?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "5"],
        "correctAnswer": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "29 - 21 =?",
        "answers": ["7", "16", "8", "24"],
        "correctAnswer": "8"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "25 - 14 =?",
        "answers": ["9", "10", "11", "16"],
        "correctAnswer": "11"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "15 - 6 =?",
        "answers": ["12", "9", "7", "8"],
        "correctAnswer": "9"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "15 - 9 =?",
        "answers": ["12", "6", "9", "3"],
        "correctAnswer": "6"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "25 - 16 =?",
        "answers": ["9", "11", "3", "7"],
        "correctAnswer": "9"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "12 - 8 =?",
        "answers": ["4", "6", "10", "2"],
        "correctAnswer": "4"
      }
    ],
  };
  